Philip tan is our operations manager
smart hardworking funny everyone loves
him recently he started getting these
serious back aches an x-ray showed that
there is a small tumor in his lower back
he has to see a doctor a surgery might
be necessary he has no idea where to
start his doctor recommended someone but
Philip couldn't tell if that specialist
had any experience in managing his
specific condition Philip has been doing
his own research he is caught in this
hamster wheel to find the right doctor
as he continues to suffer we all felt
his pain but we couldn't help he isn't
just an employee my team is my family
what can I do to help him find the right
care Prudential has heard you and we are
here to help introducing Prudential's
partnership with doc doc Asia's leading
patient empowerment company with the
largest healthcare provider network in
Asia doc talk ensures your employees can
receive personalized care and make
informed healthcare decisions without
any hassle we understand that each of
your employees have unique medical needs
and finding the right doctor can be a
scary process that is why doc doc will
assign your employees a dedicated
medical concierge who will discuss the
unique medical problems in detail after
analyzing hundreds of data points per
doctor the medical concierge will
provide a customized to report to your
employees to help them pick the right
doctor for their specific condition or
procedure
doc doc supports your employees at every
step of the way to ensure your employees
receive quality care at a fair price at
Prudential we understand that your
employees are your family to let us help
you at every step of your employees
medical journey Prudential always
listening always understanding